Airplanes
Marist College
Airplanes
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.2
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Airplanes, 2.1.1.2.2
              - Airplane pilot, two American soldiers and man in long coat, circa 1918; 72 (Box 1319)
                5x7
              - Man in long coat and French soldier standing in front of airplane, circa 1918; 73
              - Airplane pilot and man, circa 1918; 74
              - Airplane pilot and woman, circa 1918; 75
              - Airplane pilot and woman in fur coat in front of airplane, circa 1918; 76
                4x5
                film
              - Six men standing in front of airplane, circa 1918; 77
              - Airplane pilot and woman shaking hands, other pilots nearby them, circa 1918; 78
              - Six airplane pilots, circa 1918; 79
              - Airplane pilot holding cloth, circa 1918; 80
              - Airplane pilot, circa 1918; 81
              - Airplane pilot in cockpit, circa 1918; 82
              - Man sitting in airplane cockpit, circa 1918; 83
              - Airport, two airplanes inside hanger, people standing outside, circa 1918; 84
                3.5x4.75
              - Airplane in field, circa 1918; 85
              - Airplane, Chicago, two soldiers, a woman and a man in foreground, circa 1918; 86
              - Pilots, soldiers and others standing in front of the airplane Chicago, circa 1918; 87
              - Two men working on the airplane New Orleans, circa 1918; 88
              - Crowd surrounding three airplanes, one numbered “4”, circa 1918; 89
              - Crowd of spectators, flags in foreground, three airplanes in distance, circa 1918; 90
              - Military men standing, airplanes nearby, circa 1918; 91
              - Two men leaning against airplane, more airplanes in distance, circa 1918; 92
              - Many men looking at airplanes in distance, circa 1918; 93
              - Five military men and pilots facing camera, circa 1918; 94
              - Military men in front of airplane, circa 1918; 95
              - Man leaning on airplane wing watching men surrounding other airplanes, circa 1918; 96
              - Pilot in airplane facing camera, circa 1918; 97
              - United States airplane “2”, circa 1918; 1 (Box 1320)
              - United States airplane “3”, taken in air (aerial view), circa 1918; 2
              - United States airplane “3”, circa 1918; 3
              - United States airplane “3”, taken in air, passenger waving (aerial view), circa 1918; 4
              - United States airplane “3”, on water, circa 1918; 5
              - Two boats, United States airplane “3” and second airplane flying overhead, circa 1918; 6
              - United States airplanes “2” and “3”, in air, circa 1918; 7
              - United States airplane “4”, surrounded by people, in front of buildings, circa 1918; 8
              - United States airplanes “2” and “3”, with a third airplane, flying past a tall tower, circa 1918; 9
              - United States airplanes “2”, “3” and “4” flying over city, taken in air (aerial view), circa 1918; 10
              - Three airplanes flying over ships, people waving flags in foregrounds, circa 1918; 11
              - Airplane flying over ships, circa 1918; 12
              - Two airplanes flying over mountains and water, ship and buildings in foreground, circa 1918; 13
              - Two airplanes flying over mountains and water, ship and buildings in foreground, circa 1918; 14
              - United States airplane flying past mountain, large ship below, circa 1918; 15
              - Three airplanes flying over mountains covered in trees, circa 1918; 16
              - Three United States airplanes flying over fields, palms, mountains, circa 1918; 17
              - Airplane flying over ship with large sails, circa 1918; 18
              - Airplane flying past ship with two large sails, circa 1918; 19
              - Three airplanes flying over small buildings, circa 1918; 20
              - United States airplane, in air, circa 1918; 21
              - Airplane flying over ocean, circa 1918; 22
              - Airplane, viewed from another airplane (aerial view), circa 1918; 23
              - Two airplanes, attached by a wire, flying over shore (aerial view), circa 1918; 24
              - Two airplanes, attached by a wire, flying over shore (aerial view), circa 1918; 25
              - Airplane landing on water, woods and mountains in background, circa 1918; 26
              - Two airplanes on water, boat in foreground, circa 1918; 27
              - Two airplanes on water, man waving on shore in foreground, circa 1918; 28
              - Airplane on water, man with ax in foreground, circa 1918; 29
              - Two airplanes on water, tiny boat in foreground, sailboats in distance, circa 1918; 30
              - American airplane on water, pilot on pontoon, other man standing on top with hook, circa 1918; 31
              - United States airplane “3” crashed in water, circa 1918; 32
              - View of mountains from airplane (aerial view), circa 1918; 33
              - Clouds, taken from airplane, circa 1918; 34